ACTWU's Legal Department Records 5619/017
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Amalgamated Staff Retirement Plan [folder 1 of 2], 1963 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Amalgamated Staff Retirement Plan [folder 2 of 2], 1963 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Amalgamated Staff Retirement Plan [folder 1 of 2], 1964 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Amalgamated Staff Retirement Plan [folder 2 of 2], 1964 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Neckwear Insurance Fund, 1944-1961 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Amalgamated Neckwear Workers Ins. Fund Agreement and Declaration of Trust, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Neckwear Workers New York State Examination Retirement Fund, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Neckwear Union Label, 1956-1962 (Box 22, Folder 14)
- Neckwear Workers Insurance Fund Minutes of Trustees, 1955-1971 (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Shutzer, Barry, & Durant (Arbitration) Exhibits-Notes-Memoranda [folder 1 of 3], 1963 (Box 22, Folder 16)
- Shutzer, Barry, & Durant (Arbitration) Exhibits-Notes-Memoranda [folder 2 of 3], 1961 (Box 22, Folder 17)
- Shutzer, Barry, & Durant (Arbitration) Exhibits-Notes-Memoranda [folder 3 of 3], 1962 (Box 22, Folder 18)
- Rutter-Rex (Back Pay Briefs) [folder 1 of 4], 1954-1955 (Box 22, Folder 19)
- Rutter-Rex (Back Pay Briefs) [folder 2 of 4], 1964 (Box 22, Folder 20)
- Rutter-Rex (Back Pay Briefs) [folder 3 of 4], 1955 (Box 22, Folder 21)
- Rutter-Rex (Back Pay Briefs) [folder 4 of 4], 1963 (Box 22, Folder 22)
- Neckwear Insurance & Retirement Fund [folder 1 of 2], 1944-1964 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Neckwear Insurance & Retirement Fund [folder 2 of 2], 1947-1953 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Neckwear Workers Insurance Fund, 1962-1969 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Amalgamated Neckwear Insurance Fund Social Insurance & Retirement, 1961 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Neckwear Insurance & Retirement Fund, 1953-1967 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Minnesota Joint Board Arbitration Young-Quinlan Rothchild and Juster Company, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Rutter-Rex Manufacturing Company [folder 1 of 5], 1967-1968 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  March 1967-1968
- Rutter-Rex Manufacturing Company [folder 2 of 5], 1967-1968 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Rutter-Rex Manufacturing Company [folder 3 of 5], 1967-1968 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Rutter-Rex Manufacturing Company [folder 4 of 5], 1967-1968 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- Rutter-Rex Manufacturing Company [folder 5 of 5], 1967-1968 (Box 23, Folder 11)
- Rutter-Rex Manufacturing Company Supreme Court Briefs, etc., 1968-1969 (Box 23, Folder 12)
- Amalgamated Staff Retirement Plan [folder 1 of 2], 1947-1949 (Box 23, Folder 13)
- Amalgamated Staff Retirement Plan [folder 1 of 2], 1946-1948 (Box 23, Folder 14)
- Neckwear Trust Agreements Insurance, Retirement, & Supp. [folder 1 of 3], 1942-1944 (Box 23, Folder 15)
- Neckwear Trust Agreements Insurance, Retirement, & Supp. [folder 2 of 3], 1944-1948 (Box 23, Folder 16)
- Neckwear Trust Agreements Insurance, Retirement, & Supp. [folder 3 of 3], 1944 (Box 23, Folder 17)
- Local 169 Washable Fund Trust, Collective, Doctor, Nurse Agreements [folder 1 of 3], 1958-1961 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Local 169 Washable Fund Trust, Collective, Doctor, Nurse Agreements [folder 2 of 3], 1958 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Local 169 Washable Fund Trust, Collective, Doctor, Nurse Agreements [folder 3 of 3], 1943-1953 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Amalgamated Staff Retirement Plan [folder 1 of 3], 1966-1967 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Amalgamated Staff Retirement Plan [folder 2 of 3], 1966-1967 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Amalgamated Staff Retirement Plan [folder 3 of 3], 1966-1967 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Amalgamated Staff Retirement Plan [folder 1 of 4], 1968-1970 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Amalgamated Staff Retirement Plan [folder 2 of 4], 1968-1970 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Amalgamated Staff Retirement Plan [folder 3 of 4], 1968-1970 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- Amalgamated Staff Retirement Plan [folder 4 of 4], 1968-1970 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- Rutter-Rex Manufacturing Company [folder 1 of 3], 1966-1967 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  June 1966 - February 1967
- Rutter-Rex Manufacturing Company [folder 2 of 3], 1966-1967 (Box 24, Folder 12)
- Rutter-Rex Manufacturing Company [folder 3 of 3], 1966-1967 (Box 24, Folder 13)
- New York Joint Board Vacation & Holiday Fund, 1945-1964 (Box 24, Folder 14)
- New York Joint Board Staff Retirement Plan, Agreements, Audits, & Forms [folder 1 of 2], 1949-1951 (Box 24, Folder 15)
- New York Joint Board Staff Retirement Plan, Agreements, Audits, & Forms [folder 2 of 2], 1949-1968 (Box 24, Folder 16)
- Local 169 Washable Fund New Proposed Retirement Plan, 1961 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  October 1961
- Local 169 Staff Retirement Plan Minutes, 1961-1963 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  Thru October 1963
- Shutzer Misc., 1953-1973 (Box 24, Folder 19)
- Local 169 Staff Retirement Plan [folder 1 of 3], 1961-1967 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  1961 to Dec. 1967
- Local 169 Staff Retirement Plan [folder 2 of 3], 1961-1967 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Local 169 Staff Retirement Plan [folder 3 of 3], 1961-1967 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Local 169 Staff Retirement Fund [folder 1 of 4], 1959-1960 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Local 169 Staff Retirement Fund [folder 2 of 4], 1959-1960 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Local 169 Staff Retirement Fund [folder 3 of 4], 1959-1960 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Local 169 Staff Retirement Fund [folder 4 of 4], 1959-1960 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Knox Manufacturing Corp. Health Fund Bank Statements [folder 1 of 4], 1965-1971 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Knox Manufacturing Corp. Health Fund Bank Statements [folder 2 of 4], 1965-1971 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Knox Manufacturing Corp. Health Fund Bank Statements [folder 3 of 4], 1965-1971 (Box 25, Folder 10)
- Knox Manufacturing Corp. Health Fund Bank Statements [folder 4 of 4], 1965-1971 (Box 25, Folder 11)
- Cleanerama Drive-In Cleaners, Inc., 1969-1970 (Box 25, Folder 12)
- Knox Mfg. Corp. Health Fund [folder 1 of 5], 1959-1963 (Box 25, Folder 13)
- Knox Mfg. Corp. Health Fund [folder 2 of 5], 1961-1971 (Box 25, Folder 14)
- Knox Mfg. Corp. Health Fund [folder 3 of 5], 1966-1968 (Box 25, Folder 15)
- Knox Mfg. Corp. Health Fund [folder 4 of 5], 1960-1965 (Box 25, Folder 16)
- Knox Mfg. Corp. Health Fund [folder 5 of 5], 1955-1960 (Box 25, Folder 17)
- Knox Manufacturing Corp. Health Fund Financial Statements-Audit Reports [folder 1 of 4], 1961-1966 (Box 25, Folder 18)
- Knox Manufacturing Corp. Health Fund Financial Statements-Audit Reports [folder 2 of 4], 1958-1968 (Box 25, Folder 19)
- Knox Manufacturing Corp. Health Fund Financial Statements-Audit Reports [folder 3 of 4], 1962-1969 (Box 25, Folder 20)
- Knox Manufacturing Corp. Health Fund Financial Statements-Audit Reports [folder 4 of 4], 1962-1963 (Box 25, Folder 21)
- Knox Manufacturing Health Fund Trustees Bond, 1963-1966 (Box 25, Folder 22)
- Glove Workers Amalgamated Merger [folder 1 of 3], 1961-1965 (Box 25, Folder 23)
- Glove Workers Amalgamated Merger [folder 2 of 3], 1961-1965 (Box 25, Folder 24)
- Glove Workers Amalgamated Merger [folder 3 of 3], 1961-1965 (Box 25, Folder 25)
- Community Services, Inc. United Housing Foundation Memos, 1967-1972 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Community Services, Inc. President's Reports, 1968-1969 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Community Services, Inc. Financial Reports, 1968-1968 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Community Services, Inc. Other Reports [folder 1 of 2], 1968-1972 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Community Services, Inc. Other Reports [folder 2 of 2], 1968-1969 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Riverbay Corporation Memos, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Riverbay Corporation Reports, 1968-1971 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Riverbay Corporation Minutes [folder 1 of 2], 1971 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Riverbay Corporation Minutes [folder 2 of 2], 1967-1970 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- Riverbay Corporation Bylaws, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 10)
- A. Philip Randolph Institute, 1971-1972 (Box 26, Folder 11)
- Federal Trade Commission Staff Report New York Regional Office, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  May 1973
- Operations Employment Service and Unemployment Insurance, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  October 1974
- New York State Dept. of Commerce Annual Report, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 14)
- New York Job Development Authority Annual Report, 1973-1974 (Box 26, Folder 15)
- It pays to locate in New York State, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 16)
- Ninth Evaluation of the New York State Unemployment Insurance Fund, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 17)
- The Apparel Industry's Impact on New York City's Economy, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 18)
- Advance Report of Chairman to Midwinter Meeting of the Council, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  January 1972
- First Preliminary Report of the Committee on Committees, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  January 17, 1973
- Advance Report of Chairman to San Francisco Meeting of the Council, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 21)
- National Health Insurance [folder 1 of 2], 1971 (Box 26, Folder 22)
- National Health Insurance [folder 2 of 2], 1971-1972 (Box 26, Folder 23)
- David Kahn, Inc., 1967-1972 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Urban Community Insurance Company Declaration and Charter, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Urban Community Insurance Company Bylaws, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Urban Community Insurance Company Minutes of Board Meetings, 1968-1969 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Urban Community Insurance Company Minutes Exec. Comm. Meetings [folder 1 of 2], 1968-1969 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Urban Community Insurance Company Minutes Exec. Comm. Meetings [folder 2 of 2], 1967-1968 (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Urban Community Insurance Company Minutes-Invest. Comm. Meetings, 1968-1969 (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Urban Community Insurance Company Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Urban Community Insurance Company Board Meetings Notices, 1969-1970 (Box 27, Folder 9)
- Urban Community Insurance Company Board of Directors General, 1970-1971 (Box 27, Folder 10)
- J.P. Stevens & Company 11-RC-4765 Trial Notes & Briefs, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 11)
- J.P. Stevens & Co Miscellaneous (Allendale), 1974-1980 (Box 27, Folder 12)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Case #no.11-RC-4765 Election Objection & Challenges, 1979-1980 (Box 27, Folder 13)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Case no.11-RC-4765 Allendale, S.C., 1979 (Box 27, Folder 14)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Case no.11-CA-8698 Allendale, S.C., 1979 (Box 27, Folder 15)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Case no.11-CA-8707 Allendale, S.C., 1979 (Box 27, Folder 16)
- J.P. Stevens & Co, Inc. Negotiations - Allendale, S.C., 1978-1980 (Box 27, Folder 17)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Statements Allendale, S.C., 1979-1980 (Box 27, Folder 18)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Case no.11-CA-8819 Allendale, S.C., 1979-1980 (Box 27, Folder 19)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Case no.11-CA-8630 Allendale, S.C. Josie Ingram Warning, 1979-1980 (Box 27, Folder 20)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Legal Clearance [folder 1 of 6], 1977-1978 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Legal Clearance [folder 2 of 6], 1977-1978 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Legal Clearance [folder 3 of 6], 1977-1978 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Legal Clearance [folder 4 of 6], 1977-1978 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Legal Clearance [folder 5 of 6], 1977-1978 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Legal Clearance [folder 6 of 6], 1977-1978 (Box 28, Folder 6)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Boycott Materials, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 7)
- J.P. Stevens (Roanoke Rapids) Arbitration - Donna Shearin, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 8)
- J.P. Stevens (Roanoke Rapids) Demand to NLRB, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 9)
- ACTWU, Local (JPS) William Hobbs Case no.11-CB-1074, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 10)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Roanoke Rapids Jesse Lowe Arbitration, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 11)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Roanoke Rapids Melvin Barnett Grievance, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 12)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Legal IMPT., 1977 (Box 28, Folder 13)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Arbitrations, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 14)
- ACTWU, Local no.1948 AFL-CIO J.P. Stevens (Roanoke Rapids) Case no.11-CB-1183, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 15)
- J.P. Stevens & Company (Fleming Discharge) Roanoke Rapids - Transcript, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 16)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Donna Shearin Grievance, 1981-1983 (Box 28, Folder 17)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Allendale Closing, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 18)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Credit Union, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  January 7, 1983
- J.P. Stevens & Company Arbitration, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 20)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Roanoke Rapids, 1979-1985 (Box 28, Folder 21)
- J.P. Stevens (Arbitration) Billy Hux (Roanoke Rapids), 1982-1983 (Box 28, Folder 22)
- J.P. Stevens & Company ACTWU Agreement, 1980-1982 (Box 28, Folder 23)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Cecil Adkins Arbitration Roanoke Rapids, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 24)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Roanoke Rapids (Plant no.2) Jerry W. Spence Discharge, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 25)
- J.P. Stevens & Company ACTWU Arbitration, 1982-1983 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Case no.11-CB-1402 Roanoke Rapids, N.C., 1985 (Box 29, Folder 2)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Roanoke Rapids, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Case no.11-CB-1473 Roanoke Rapids, N.C., 1986 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Roanoke Rapids, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 5)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Harry T. Robinson Discharge, 1982-1983 (Box 29, Folder 6)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Bargaining Correspondence Roanoke Rapids, 1977-1978 (Box 29, Folder 7)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Wallace N.C. (Willie Brice), 1978 (Box 29, Folder 8)
- J.P. Stevens & Company (Roanoke Rapids) Workmens Compensation, 1977 (Box 29, Folder 9)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Wages, 1977 (Box 29, Folder 10)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Employment Analysis Report Program, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 11)
- J.P. Stevens & Company EEO-1 Report, 1974-1978 (Box 29, Folder 12)
- J.P. Stevens Co. Bargaining Notes Roanoke Rapids [folder 1 of 3], 1977 (Box 29, Folder 13)
- J.P. Stevens Co. Bargaining Notes Roanoke Rapids [folder 2 of 3], 1976 (Box 29, Folder 14)
- J.P. Stevens Co. Bargaining Notes Roanoke Rapids [folder 3 of 3], 1976-1977 (Box 29, Folder 15)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. New Milford II-1-CA-15416 & 1-CA-16314 (Settlement), 1984 (Box 29, Folder 16)
- J.P. Stevens & Company History of Elections, 1977 (Box 29, Folder 17)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Roanoke Rapids, NC Contract for Videotape of Contract Ratification, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 18)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Roanoke Rapids Petition for Certiorari, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 19)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Roanoke Rapids Subpoena, 1976-1977 (Box 29, Folder 20)
- J.P. Stevens & Company To Be Analyzed, 1977-1978 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Roanoke Rapids Transcripts (Refusal to Bargain), 1974 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Other Factors, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 3)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Extra Material, 1974-1976 (Box 30, Folder 4)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Correspondence for Trial, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 5)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Correspondence for Trial, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  Sept. 14 - Dec. 2 1976
- J.P. Stevens & Company Roanoke Rapids, N.C. Refusal to Bargain, 1976-1978 (Box 30, Folder 7)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Exhibits R CP, 1974-1976 (Box 30, Folder 8)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Action File, 1978-1980 (Box 30, Folder 9)
- J.P. Stevens Co. Boycott, 1978-1980 (Box 30, Folder 10)
- J.P. Stevens Co. Corporate Campaign, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 11)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Roanoke Rapids Trials, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 12)
- J.P. Stevens Company Material, 1976-1977 (Box 30, Folder 13)
- J.P. Stevens Co. Corporate Campaign, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 14)
- J.P. Stevens Co. Church Groups Student Committees Organizations, 1976-1977 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- J.P. Stevens & Co. Canada, 1977 (Box 31, Folder 2)
- J.P. Stevens & Co. Corporate Campaign, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 3)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Corporate Campaign, 1977 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Boycott, 1979-1980 (Box 31, Folder 5)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Boycott, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 6)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Correspondence, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 7)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Correspondence [folder 1 of 2], 1978 (Box 31, Folder 8)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Correspondence [folder 2 of 2], 1978 (Box 31, Folder 9)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Correspondence, 1975-1977 (Box 31, Folder 10)
- Crystal Lee Sutton Media Coverage Report, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 11)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Fact Sheets, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 12)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Financial, 1976-1980 (Box 31, Folder 13)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Heritage Foundation, 1977 (Box 31, Folder 14)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Legal, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 15)
- J.P. Stevens & Company International, 1976-1980 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Legal, 1980 (Box 32, Folder 2)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Legal, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 3)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Legal, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 4)
- U.S. District Court Albert Gandy Deposition, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 5)
- U.S. District Court William L. Wall Deposition [folder 1 of 3], 1979 (Box 32, Folder 6)
- U.S. District Court William L. Wall Deposition [folder 2 of 3], 1979 (Box 32, Folder 7)
- U.S. District Court William L. Wall Deposition [folder 3 of 3], 1979 (Box 32, Folder 8)
- U.S. District Court Charles Osborne Deposition, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 9)
- U.S. District Court Joe M. Tate Deposition, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 10)
- U.S. District Court William Zarkowsky Deposition, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 11)
- U.S. District Court Appendix VIII, 1976-1978 (Box 32, Folder 12)
- ACTWU v. Rice - Milledgeville Grumman Aerospace Corporation, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 13)
- J.P. Stevens & Co. Charging Party's Brief, 1977 (Box 32, Folder 14)
- U.S. District Court Appendix I, 1979 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- J.P. Stevens & Co. Legal, 1979 (Box 33, Folder 2)
- J.P. Stevens & Co. Legal, 1979-1981 (Box 33, Folder 3)
- U.S. District Court Deposition of Robert v. Rice [folder 1 of 2], 1979 (Box 33, Folder 4)
- U.S. District Court Deposition of Robert v. Rice [folder 2 of 2], 1979 (Box 33, Folder 5)
- Milledgeville Materials, 1978-1979 (Box 33, Folder 6)
- J.P. Stevens & Co. For Distribution, 1979 (Box 33, Folder 7)
- U.S. District Court Robert Rice Deposition, 1979 (Box 33, Folder 8)
- U.S. District Court William L. McDermott Deposition, 1979 (Box 33, Folder 9)
- U.S. District Court Charles J. Briscoe Deposition, 1979 (Box 33, Folder 10)
- U.S. District Court Thomas Rozzi Deposition, 1979 (Box 33, Folder 11)
- ACTWU v. Rice Depositions [folder 1 of 2], 1979 (Box 33, Folder 12)
- ACTWU v. Rice Depositions [folder 2 of 2], 1979 (Box 33, Folder 13)
- ACTWU v. Rice Memos, 1979-1980 (Box 33, Folder 14)
- ACTWU v. Rice Memos, 1980 (Box 33, Folder 15)
- ACTWU v. Rice Legal, 1979 (Box 33, Folder 16)
- ACTWU v. Rice Memos, 1979-1980 (Box 33, Folder 17)
- ACTWU v. Rice Milledgeville, GA Duplicate Documents, 1979-1980 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- J.P. Stevens & Company FTC, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 2)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Documents, 1987 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  November 6, 1987
- J.P. Stevens & Company General File, 1983 (Box 34, Folder 4)
- J.P. Stevens & Company General, 1981-1988 (Box 34, Folder 5)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Insurance Raynor Request for Info., 1981-1983 (Box 34, Folder 6)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Settlement Agreement & Collective Bargaining Agreement, 1985 (Box 34, Folder 7)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Arbitration, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 8)
- J.P. Stevens & Co. Port Huron, Michigan, 1985-1986 (Box 34, Folder 9)
- J.P. Stevens & Co., Inc. Easthampton Election, 1983 (Box 34, Folder 10)
- J.P. Stevens Contracts, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 11)
- J.P. Stevens, Co. Inc. Bennett Taylor (Perfect) Attendance Grievance, 1982-1983 (Box 34, Folder 12)
- J.P. Stevens & Co. Inc. Grievance of Yvonne Wilhelm, 1982-1983 (Box 34, Folder 13)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Members Only Credit Union, 1982 (Box 34, Folder 14)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Quality Program, 1982 (Box 34, Folder 15)
- J.P. Stevens Gimbels II, 1978-1979 (Box 34, Folder 16)
- J.P. Stevens & Co. Ray Schmidt, 1978-1980 (Box 34, Folder 17)
- J.P. Stevens Eddie Sykes, 1986 (Box 34, Folder 18)
- J.P. Stevens & Co. ACTWU vs. Gimbels Bros. Southern District of New York, 1979-1980 (Box 34, Folder 19)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Maynard Lovell, 1978-1980 (Box 34, Folder 20)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Memo's on Store Picketing, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 21)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Follow-Up File, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 22)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Lewis vs. J.P. Stevens, 1981 (Box 34, Folder 23)
- J.P. Stevens Company, Inc. Proposed Insurance Changes, 1981 (Box 34, Folder 24)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Case no.11-CB-1519 (Hattie Kee) Failure to Process, 1987 (Box 34, Folder 25)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Wage Re-Opener, 1983 (Box 34, Folder 26)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Norma Rae, 1979-1980 (Box 34, Folder 27)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Boycott, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 28)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Stevens Workers, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 29)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Union Posters, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 30)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Case no.11-CB-1303, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 1)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Continuity of Contractual Obligations, 1985-1988 (Box 35, Folder 2)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Drake Branch VA, 1986 (Box 35, Folder 3)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Case no.5-CA-19416 Drakes Branch Plant VA, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 4)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Drakes Branch VA Case no.5-RC-12976, 1987-1988 (Box 35, Folder 5)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Agreement with ACTWU, 1980 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  10-19-1985
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. NLRB No. 79-1247 No. 79-1254, 1979 (Box 35, Folder 7)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Case no.11-CA-6077 no.11-RC-3987, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  5/1/1978
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Case No. 79-7631 [folder 1 of 2], 1979 (Box 35, Folder 9)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Case No. 79-7631 [folder 2 of 2], 1979 (Box 35, Folder 10)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. No. 79-1247 & No.79-1254 Brief, 1979 (Box 35, Folder 11)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Court Report, 1979 (Box 35, Folder 12)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Documents, 1974 (Box 36, Folder 1)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Documents, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  January-June 1975
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Documents, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  July-December 1975
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Documents, 1973 (Box 36, Folder 4)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Documents, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 5)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Miscellaneous, 1972 (Box 37, Folder 1)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Miscellaneous, 1968-1975 (Box 37, Folder 2)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Statesboro, Georgia, 1972-1976 (Box 37, Folder 3)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Roanoke Rapids, North Carolina, 1973-1976 (Box 37, Folder 4)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Insurance Case, 1975 (Box 37, Folder 5)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. ACTWU, 1979-1980 (Box 37, Folder 6)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. 77-CIV-5444 Discovery Employee Committee, 1978-1983 (Box 37, Folder 7)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. North Carolina Fund for Individual Rights, 1979-1980 (Box 37, Folder 8)
- Education v. J.P. Stevens Education Committee [folder 1 of 4], 1980 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  7-16-1980
- Education v. J.P. Stevens Education Committee [folder 2 of 4], 1980 (Box 37, Folder 10)
- Education v. J.P. Stevens Education Committee [folder 3 of 4], 1980 (Box 37, Folder 11)
- Education v. J.P. Stevens Education Committee [folder 4 of 4], 1980-1981 (Box 37, Folder 12)
- Marshall v. JPSEEC, Hutchens, and SPFFF Decision of IV, Materials Regarding Subpoena Enforcement, 1980-1981 (Box 37, Folder 13)
- ACTWU vs. J.P. Stevens (77-CIV-5444) Disposition Martin Processing Co. Julious Hermes, John Haukins, 1978-1979 (Box 38, Folder 1)
- Patterson v. NLRB Briefs to IV and Supreme Court Decisions, 1980-1981 (Box 38, Folder 2)
- JPSEEC v. NLRB, 1977 (Box 38, Folder 3)
- Education Committee(s)- Financial & "Moral Support" Connections - Contributors, 1977-1979 (Box 38, Folder 4)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. (77-CIV-5444) Georgia Synthetics Inc. Deposition, 1978 (Box 38, Folder 5)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Department of Labor (LMRDA), 1979-1983 (Box 38, Folder 6)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. ACTWU, 1979-1982 (Box 38, Folder 7)